{
    "id": "f8593195b9864571b865a627d39d3784",
    "title": "Intermediate Level Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ................................. him for the past month.",
            "description": "Perfect tenses are preferred with the prepositions for and since.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't meet",
                "haven't met",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Professionals .......................... as doctors and teachers should show social commitment.",
            "description": "The correct expression is 'such as'. Or you can use 'like'.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "like",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor, ........................... saw me in the morning, insisted that I should quit smoking.",
            "description": "Both who and that can refer to people however, we cannot use that in non-identifying relative clauses. Here the commas indicate that the relative clause is non-identifying. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't want to see ..............................",
            "description": "In questions and negatives we use 'any' or 'anyone'. ",
            "answers": [
                "anyone",
                "no one",
                "someone"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house .......................... I was born.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which.",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The house ........................... I was born in is made of clay.",
            "description": "Where can mean in which. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "where",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "His failure didn't bother him .............................. the least.",
            "description": "The correct expression is 'in the least'.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ....................... a pretty girl.",
            "description": "We use 'so' before an adjective we use 'such' before an adjective + noun.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... the people invited to the party didn't turn up.",
            "description": "We use 'many of' before a noun with a determiner (the, my, this etc.)",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "In accordance ............................ your request, we are sending you some samples.",
            "description": "In accordance with is the correct expression. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That is the best film I .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever saw",
                "have ever seen",
                "have never seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Where .................................... all this while?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were",
                "have you been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}